It has begun! Ana channel applause!
Today's guest is this person's person!
Yes!
These are the people!
Yes! Please!
Hashday! This is Yanagawa!
Hello!
Anna, are you okay with shouting?
I'm not very good at it, but I'm fine.
Okay! Then I'll try to keep my voice down.
Raise it!
I'm Iwakura from Frog Store! Please!
You don't have to leave it as "Arakawa".
It's not arakawa!
You look like him.
It was the same earlier. I've been doing it for a long time.
I'm sorry, I didn't do it.
You have to believe me.
Believe me, I'm sure now.
You didn't see anyone.
What was today?
Today we're going for a drive as gals.
I'd like you to be my gals today.
We'll go for a drive together.
Driving around in gal makeup? That sounds great!
I often do gal makeup on comedians.
I never thought I'd be able to do gal makeup for Anochan-san.
I brought a lot of things that I thought would give a different impression.
I brought color contacts and such, but I was told that I could freely do that as well.
That was great.
Awesome!
Sei is cute and sweet. I'm glad. We often talk about her when we're drinking.
She's really cute.
That makes me happy.
But he also talked to me when we were on London Hearts before.
I thought you were really nice to me then.
I didn't know you remembered me.
Of course. Of course.
Glad to hear it.
I thought I was the opposite.
I thought I was the opposite of you, so I'm glad the earth is round.
I'm glad that we're all on the same side, and I'd really like to see what a gal looks like today.
Have you ever been a gal before?
I'm not used to it.
You're too cute! Let's do it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What happened to Ms. Iwakura after that? Where's Ms. Iwakura?
Where's Ms. Iwakura?
Mr. Iwakura?
Where's Ms. Iwakura? Please tell me all the waitresses in the store have one of these.
You're so cute!
I don't want to break everyone's pace by making too much noise, so I'm trying to keep up with them in my own way, but it's true.
But you're right, you're the complete opposite of Ms. Iwakura.
It's true that I admire gyaru.
I like unfamiliar gals a lot.
Why is that?
Gyaru are very energetic, just by being around them.
They're like the sun.
Gal affirms everything and doesn't deny it.
That makes me happy.
Then I'd like to start with color contacts.
Okay.
Achan, are you sure these will look good?
I think these will look good, too.
But I'd like you to try these pink ones.
They're minus four, so they're fine. This is minus four, so it's okay.
I'll just put this on.
This one has a video of Anochan.
Oh, sorry.
No, no, no, no.
Please communicate with Mr. Iwakura.
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Who are you imitating?
I'm sorry, I didn't recognize you... but you look better now.
It definitely doesn't suit you, but you're so cute.
No, it's not.
With the contacts.
You're so cute!
So cute!
Extremely cute.
They still look very uncomfortable.
You don't wear very big ones?
I don't wear colored ones very often.
You put them on very roughly.
You're so fast.
Okay, next.
May I see them with you?
Okay.
I'll just apply a little eye shadow.
Brown.
And glitter.
Sparkle under the eyes, too.
And put on a pair of false eyelashes to complete the look.
I'll do it.
I've got sores on my skin right now.
Why is it?
It's okay, it's okay. Yes, the same color? Yes, the same color!
It's the same color.
It's good, isn't it?
Okay, excuse me.
Wow.
It's like a makeup video that comes around every once in a while.
Oh, really? Oh, really?
I often work with comedians.
Moriyama-san is one of them.
I don't know what to call them... animalistic comedians.
I mean, not in a bad way, but there are a lot of big guys.
I'm sorry, can you close your eyes?
Can you close your eyes?
How long have you been a Gallo?
Since birth.
Oh, wow.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Are you self-taught in makeup?
Self-taught.
I like it dark.
Has anything good happened to you lately, Manochan?
Something good?
I don't know.
Nothing at all.
I'm just tired.
Why?
I don't have time to sleep.
Too busy to sleep?
I did it yesterday at the concert.
Are you tired then?
I'm a little tired.
Yeah, let's turn it up a notch.
Excuse the glitter.
Can I get a little fringe?
I'm sorry.
That's such a wet sound.
Yes, a little glitter.
Glitter.
Excuse me.
Anna, if you could sleep, would you sleep a lot?
I would love to sleep a lot.
I've always loved sleeping. I've always been a huge fan of sleeping.
You like it?
Yes, my eyes don't open very much these days.
Sleepy?
Sleepy, I guess. And when I see sunlight, I start to cry.
Oh, my.
So, please make your eyes pop.
Okay, I'll do it. I'll leave it to you. Eyes that won't lose to the sun.
Yes, I'll do it.
I'll let you make the most of it.
Okay, brown eyeshadow on top.
Yes, I'll do it.
Apply this all over, and then apply it to the double width of the eye.
Please do it.
What is this?
It's called glitter, and it's brown glitter.
Arakawa made this.
That's right. Arakawa made this one.
This is the one to extend.
What's "Gals"?
Yes, Gals.
I'm not going to make a mirror ball for your eyes.
I'm honestly afraid that Iwakura-san is the cutest, but now she's the cutest... and I'm really starting to feel like my head is about to explode.
I'm thinking of putting on the false eyelashes and the tight fitting ones first.
Are Iwakura and Anochan going to be together?
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to say anything before.
You ranked me No. 1 at Rondo Hearts the other day, didn't you?
I really think so.
I want to be born again.
If you were born again, who would you want to be?
No. 1?
I know.
You were number 3, right?
Yes, actually, third place.
I came in third in the eyes of the public.
I knew it. It was a gal who came in first.
Who was it?
I'm sorry, I didn't get to see that. I'm sorry I didn't see it, but...
Michoppa and Nikoru
They are the strongest, aren't they?
They are so strong!
The strongest twins!
Do you have any juniors that you are close to?
I don't have a concept of juniors.
I guess not.
I haven't lived in a vertical society for a long time.
I don't know.
Artists don't have the same sense of junior and senior, and there aren't many people who are close to them to begin with.
Oh, I see.
Excuse me.
I can do it. Wait a minute. I'm sorry. My stomach's rumbling.
Sorry. It's a long nail.
Is it okay if I sleep?
Yes. Just go back to sleep. Just rest. I'm sorry, I'm a little nervous.
Excuse me.
What's this? Glue it on.
I'll use two layers of glue to make my eyes pop.
I don't think I look good with eyelashes.
No, I think they look good.
My nose is running.
It's going to sting a little bit.
I've probably had my nails stuck a few times on the top.
Suna-chan!
I'll add a little more
I'll add some glue.
Your vision is black.
That's nice. It looks good.
Can you open it?
Oh, wow!
Cute!
Wow!
It looks like a bug's crawling.
It sure did before.
I was on the first floor. I was on the first floor.
Are you sure? Doesn't it hurt?
Am I on the floor? That's my eye.
I don't know. I'm used to it.
Does it hurt your eyes?
My eyes don't hurt.
Good.
You've had it done once, so you're used to it.
Yes, I am.
Mr. Iwakura has done it twice already.
I see... twice.
Remember what I taught you, a little at a time.
That's nice.
I think there's a black line
I think there are some black lines.
I'd like to make it a little darker.
I'd like to create tear troughs.
Are tear troughs important?
Tear troughs are really important.
They are the most important part of the body.
I'm going to the rape... I'm going to the wedding... I'm going to the wedding... I'm going to the wedding... I'm going to the wedding... I'm going to the wedding... I have 3 important tear troughs.
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Please don't look at my eyes, it's a little embarrassing.
I'm a little embarrassed.
May I ask you to look up?
Very nice.
Your eyelashes are long.
I've read in books that my eyelashes are kind of long.
But I always pull them out.
I've been following Anochan's sns for a while now, but I don't like this kind of thing.
I've been following your sns for a while now, and you've made it clear you don't like this kind of thing.
I think that's great. I get into it too much, but I can't resist.
I think it's a good thing, but you don't say.
It takes courage.
It takes courage to say no.
Do you ever think, "I don't like this. Do you ever think, "I don't like this," or "I don't like that.
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
No, no, no, I'm not such a good person.
I'm not such a good person.
It's normal, isn't it?
That's why there are so many people who support you.
People who think they'll follow you.
Upstairs, please.
Excuse me.
I used to say that too.
In the past...
If a girl pissed me off...
I'd say, "Piss off.
"Suck it?
Like, "Kusasare ga?
I'd say, "Kusasare ga, kusasare ga? Like, "Kusasare ga?
Kusare ga?
I try not to say it as much as possible.
But it stresses me out.
I've recently seen it on Instagram.
It's like a notebook.
What's it called?
Only people who follow you can see it.
Fans and the public can't see it.
Yes.
I often say bad things in there to relieve stress.
I saw something like that.
It's not bad-mouthing.
It's more like a statement.
I'm just saying what I'm thinking.
Look at that.
I sent you a stamp, right?
She sent a stamp of fire.
Like, "Let's do our best.
I felt the same way.
I think you two have some similarities. There's something similar about you two, isn't there?
You're both very attractive.
Really.
Really, really...
It's not like I'm just saying random things.
Really?
Really, really.
You don't seem like you're lying.
No lies today.
Today.
No lies.
Okay, excuse me.
What's that?
Oh, this is a big piece of glitter, and I'm going to put it right here in the corner of your eye, and I'm going to make it sparkle here, too.
And now, if you'll excuse me.
Can you put it on too, Iwakura-san?
Thank you very much.
Here.
Mr. Iwakura, you're not following me.
Should I put it on myself?
I'll do it myself.
I'll try it myself.
Please put these on.
It's kind of nice.
I'd rather be a comedian than someone in that kind of relationship.
I don't know if I'd still be a comedian if it weren't for you.
But is there anyone you can trust around you?
Well...
I'm trying to be good about it, but...
I've insured myself against betrayal at any time.
I understand that, but...
I'd like to make my tear ducts a little more shiny next time, so...
I want to make them all my own.
That's right, I'm not really advertising.
So please don't worry. Yes, don't worry.
But it looks good.
It's really sparkling.
Please look up
It will sparkle again.
The tear troughs are so beautiful to begin with.
I wanted to do it without adding any color.
A little pink.
I'm sorry, I put on too much color.
It looks really good.
I put on too much, but...
Look at the top.
What are those nails?
Why are they so long?
I can't stop it.
Are these real fingers?
My real fingers are like this.
I can't stand it.
What? Is it glue? What?
Sometimes it's glue when you break it.
It's gonna be so crippled.
I can't do anything.
I could do almost anything.
Almost, and a little bit with the wig.
Yes.
That's not quite right.
Okay, one last thing.
Thank you very much.
Look up, please.
Look up!
But you and Ana look alike, don't you?
In a good way.
When I was invited to Anochan's show.
I did an imitation of her.
Anochan's?
I mimicked Ano-chan.
I don't call myself Ano-chan.
She told me that she had finished her makeup. I'd like to say that I've completed my makeup.
Then I'd like to call Ana-chan.
Ana-chan!
Wow, she's cute, super cute...
She's so cute... I don't know if it's gonna be okay, I'm so anxious.
Super cute... so cute...
Is there anything I can say to make you feel like a gal?
Like how to talk?
Peace? All of you!
Let's do it! Let's do it!
I'm glad. It might lift my spirits a little.
It might lift your spirits a little.
It's kind of uplifting.
Really?
I feel stronger.
I feel really good, too, but I can't see very well.
My vision is bad, my vision is bad.
It's always been black.
Are you sure?
I've got eyes in my eyes.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Departure...
Departure progression!
Honey Flash!
There it is!
What a great group to drive with!
Are you going to the beach with us?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
Where's the gal?
That's her.
That's why she's at the beach.
But your skin is really white outside.
No, not at all.
You don't go outside much?
Not at all.
Yes, I do.
Yes, you do. It's out, yes, it's out.
It's coming out.
You're leaving?
What are you doing?
I often go out for a drink at night.
With whom?
What do you talk about?
I was so drunk I don't remember much.
I've been so drunk I can barely remember.
Listen, Crystal, you're still too cool.
Let me be honest... he's cool.
I'm Ariyoshi's wall... and I like samurai.
Noda-san dressed as a samurai is really cool.
you like samurai, don't you?
I like samurai so much that I want to be in a period drama.
I really want to be in a period drama.
You want to be in a period drama?
But Noda-san is so cool.
He looks good as a samurai.
I tell Mr. Iwakura everything.
She's like a mother to me.
He's so nice.
But I'm a terrible conversationalist.
I'm in love with people... people I like a lot.
But I don't talk much.
That's what's been bothering me lately.
What's a listener?
Listeners...
And listeners, too.
They say what they want to say all at once.
But then they say nothing.
They're in a daze the whole time.
That's right.
Like staring at tuna and natto in a daze.
I'm the same way.
I feel a little closer to you.
Conversation. Conversation.
Conversation is difficult.
Difficult.
Hmm.
You two talk freely.
But...
Mr. Arakawa's favorite song.
Why are you smiling?
What is your favorite song, Mr. Arakawa?
It's Ayu! Ayu? Ayu, are you smiling? What is it by the month?
I already like it, and I also like "Lying Gal" songs.
I also like the ones that are popular in Tik-Tok as it is.
I really like that culture.
I like songs. Now? I'm going for a drive.
What?
Sing your favorite song, Ayumi.
Sing it for me.
Are you sure?
If I say "drive," you sing.
Is that okay?
Yes.
We're on this road to happiness
We're on this journey to be happy. Look at that smile.
You look so good.
That's what I'm talking about. I love the lyrics, too.
And here we are!
Quickly!
Pien
Pien is almost over
It's almost over
I want you both to keep smiling!
If you are having a hard time, please always tell me
I'm all ears!
I really had a great time today!
I even got to be pretty!
Really?
Really? Really?
Really.
We're all connected by the gal bond, aren't we?
I just wanted to have a little more fun.
I wanted to play a little more.
I want to go to Purikura.
Wow.
I want to go to a Purikura with this channel.
I want to go to the city.
I want to go to the city with this.
I want to go.
Let's go for a drive, take Purikura pictures, and eat curry.
Yes, please.
I can't make love, I feel like I'll become a white cloud.